{
    "subject":"Literature in English",
    "topics":
    [
        {
            "topic":"Poetry",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"which of the following is a type of poetry",
                    "opt1":"pastoral",
                    "opt2":"piraesque",
                    "opt3":"political",
                    "opt4":"tragedy",
                    "ans":"pastoral"
                },
                {
                    "question":"whom of the following is a well known poet",
                    "opt1":"Shakespear",
                    "opt2":"Mary.J.Blige",
                    "opt3":"Will Smith",
                    "opt4":"Demi Lovato",
                    "ans":"Shakespear"
                },

                {
                    "question":"Which is not a characteristic of poetry",
                    "opt1":"it is usually beautiful",
                    "opt2":"it operates on acts and scenes",
                    "opt3":"it consists of rhytmic line",
                    "opt4":"it tends to have a rhyming pattern",
                    "ans":"it tends to have a rhyming pattern"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Poetry is a form of art",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"A sonnet is one stanza poem of fifteen lines",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"False"
                },
                {
                    "question":"A simple grouping of syllables, some stressed, some unstressed is called a ",
                    "opt1":"simple poetry",
                    "opt2":"frame",
                    "opt3":"foot",
                    "opt4":"elegy",
                    "ans":"foot"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"literary concepts/study of literature",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"literature has over three literary genres",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"False"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Forms of literature include all except",
                    "opt1":"poetry",
                    "opt2":"short stories",
                    "opt3":"letters",
                    "opt4":"pearl",
                    "ans":"pearl"
                },

                {
                    "question":"a ballad is a form of literature",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"which of the following is a literary term",
                    "opt1":"ballad",
                    "opt2":"gable",
                    "opt3":"panegyric",
                    "opt4":"safiro",
                    "ans":"ballad"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Emmanuel represents a lion on the field is a",
                    "opt1":"metaphor",
                    "opt2":"simile",
                    "opt3":"personification",
                    "opt4":"euphemism",
                    "ans":"personification"
                },
                {
                    "question":"The protagonist could be the hero or the villain",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"Drama",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"Drama is one of the literary genres",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Drama consists of",
                    "opt1":"acts",
                    "opt2":"stanzas",
                    "opt3":"chapters",
                    "opt4":"rhyming scheme",
                    "ans":"acts"
                },

                {
                    "question":"A tragic character is one who arouses pity and",
                    "opt1":"Terror",
                    "opt2":"Sympathy",
                    "opt3":"Horror",
                    "opt4":"Frustration",
                    "ans":"Sympathy"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Juxtaposition of contrasting ideas in any lierary work is know as",
                    "opt1":"Drama",
                    "opt2":"Oxymoron",
                    "opt3":"Synedoche",
                    "opt4":"Catharsis",
                    "ans":"Oxymoron"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Tragic comedy is a form of drama",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Any work written in act and scene is known as",
                    "opt1":"Drama",
                    "opt2":"Poem",
                    "opt3":"Prose",
                    "opt4":"Elegy",
                    "ans":"Drama"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"Prose",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"A prose deals with literary principles",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Forms of prose include",
                    "opt1":"Biography",
                    "opt2":"Comedy",
                    "opt3":"Ballad",
                    "opt4":"Time-rick",
                    "ans":"Biography"
                },

                {
                    "question":"which of the following could be applicable to all genres",
                    "opt1":"Narration",
                    "opt2":"Rhythm",
                    "opt3":"Action",
                    "opt4":"Symbolism",
                    "ans":"Narration"
                },
                {
                    "question":"All are types of prose except",
                    "opt1":"quest",
                    "opt2":"maturation",
                    "opt3":"ascension",
                    "opt4":"cast",
                    "ans":"cast"
                },
                {
                    "question":"prose is written in",
                    "opt1":"Chapters",
                    "opt2":"Stanzas",
                    "opt3":"Repetition",
                    "opt4":"Covers",
                    "ans":"Chapters"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Prose is always Fiction",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"False"
                }
                
            ]
        }
        
    ]
}
